http://www.artpridenj.com/privacy

Privacy Policy
This statement addresses the collection, use, and security of and access to information that may be obtained through the use of this website.
Information Collected and Stored Automatically
If you do nothing during your visit but browse through the website, read pages, or download information, we will gather and store certain non-personal information about your visit automatically. We use this information in a variety of ways, including to help analyze site traffic and to understand our user’s needs and trends and to improve our services. We may use your non-personal information by itself or aggregate it with information we have obtained from others.
This information does not identify you personally and made include the following: the Internet protocol (IP) address (a number automatically assigned to your computer whenever you access the Internet) used to access our website; the date and time you access our site; the pages you visit; if you linked to us from another website, the address of that site.
We use this information to help us make our site more useful to visitors by learning about the number of visitors to our site and the types of technology our visitors use.
Personal Information and Choice
You may choose to provide personal information when you interact with us, such as when you register for membership, make a donation, purchase a service, or submit a question.
“Personal information” is information about a natural person that is readily identifiable to that specific individual. Personal information includes such things as an individual’s name, address, phone number, email address, social media account information, or credit card information.
We collect no personal information about you unless you provide it voluntarily. When this information is submitted, your contact information is automatically added to our database and can be used for correspondence which we may send you. We do not locally store any financial data. You may contact us to opt out of this database at any time.
We will take reasonable steps to ensure the accuracy of the personal information we retain about you. It is your responsibility to ensure you submit true, accurate, and complete information to us, and that you update us in a timely manner if your information changes. You may request that any inaccurate or incomplete personal information held by us or on our behalf is corrected by using this site’s Contact Us form.
We may occasionally make names and mailing addresses available to other arts and cultural organizations. We do not share email addresses.
Other Information We Collect
Our services may use “cookies” and similar technologies (collectively, "Cookies"). Cookies are small text files that this website sends to your computer for record-keeping purposes and this information is stored in a file on your computer’s hard drive. Cookies make web surfing and browsing easier for you by saving your preferences so that we can use these to improve your next visit to our website.
We may use Google Analytics and/or Webtrends, to help us get a better understanding of how visitors use this website.
The information generated by the Webtrends cookie, about your use of this website, is transmitted to and stored by Webtrends. If you do not want your activity on this website to be tracked by Webtrends, you may find information about opting out by using this link: https://kb.webtrends.com/articles/Information/Opting-out-of-Tracking-Cookies-1365447872915
The information generated by the Google Analytics cookie, about your use of this website, is transmitted to and stored by Google. If you do not want your activity on this website to be tracked by Google Analytics, you may opt out by using this link: https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en.
We or third parties may use invisible pixels or beacons, as well as track server logs, on this website to count how many users visit certain pages. This information is collected and reported either in the aggregate or anonymously. We may use this information to improve our content, and to better address the needs of our users when they use this website and/or other sites.
We may receive your personal information from other sources, such as public databases, social media platforms, from people with whom you are friends or otherwise connected on social media platforms, as well as from other third parties. For example, if you elect to connect your social media account to your website account, certain personal information from your social media account will be shared with us, which may include personal information that is part of your public profile, or your friends' public profiles.
Security
We have taken several steps to safeguard the integrity of its data and prevent unauthorized access to information maintained. These measures are designed and intended to prevent corruption of data, block unknown or unauthorized access to our systems and information, and to provide reasonable protection of private information in our possession.
This site uses the industry standard encryption software Secure Socket Layer (SSL) to enable secure transmission of data. The URL in your browser will change to "HTTPS" instead of "HTTP" when this security feature is used. Your browser may also display a "padlock" or "key" symbol on its task bar to indicate a secure transmission. If these indicators are not present, information may be susceptible to interception by other parties. Most internet email communication is not considered secure.
Please note that we are not responsible for the collection, usage and disclosure of policies and practices, including the data security, of other organizations, such as Facebook, Apple, Google, Microsoft, or any other app developer, app provider, social media platform provider, operating system provider, wireless service provider or device manufacturer, including any personal information you disclose to other organizations through or in connection with the apps or our social media pages.
External Links
We may provide links to various third-party websites. However, even if an affiliation exists between ArtPride and that third-party site, we exercise no control over linked sites, each of which maintains independent privacy and data collection policies and procedures. If you visit a website which is linked from us, you should consult that site’s privacy policy before providing any personally identifying information.
Privacy Policy Changes
If we decide to make any changes to our privacy policy, we will post those changes here so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information, and whether we will disclose it to anyone.
Contact Us
Mail:
ArtPride New Jersey Foundation
432 High Street, First Floor
Burlington, New Jersey 08016
Phone:
609.479.3377
Online:
